{
    "subject": "resource/WPKN",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "WPKN",
    "human_readable": "The name of WPKN is WPKN.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9738814830780029,
            "question": "What is the name of WPKN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7441959381103516,
            "question": "Where is WPKN located?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7281594276428223,
            "question": "Is WPKN a radio station?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7049177885055542,
            "question": "Who are the hosts on WPKN?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6778481602668762,
            "question": "When was WPKN founded?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6646121144294739,
            "question": "What genre of music does WPKN play?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6094199419021606,
            "question": "Does WPKN have a website?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5950707793235779,
            "question": "What events does WPKN host?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5764023661613464,
            "question": "Does WPKN have a social media presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5221845507621765,
            "question": "Is WPKN affiliated with any other organizations?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of WPKN is WPKN.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4969_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does WPKN have a social media presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4969_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What events does WPKN host?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4969_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does WPKN have a website?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4969_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4969_88.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe information provided in the documents supports that WPKN is indeed the name of the radio station."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}